[ED.
Last Practice
Last practice.
How's it going?
Well! I'm not really feeling it yet.
I'm just a little nervous.
I'm nervous. I want to do my best.
How was it yesterday?
I enjoyed the show yesterday.
But there's a ceremony today.
I have to do my best.
I'm off to the boiler.
Have a good day. What are you doing?
I'm going to sing a little.
Does everyone know by now?
It's not like it's a secret.
I'm going to start with the insta-video, which you can't click on.
Me.
I was standing alone somewhere in a city I don't know.
They know who I am.
Hey, can someone please tell me what's going on? I'm just going through the motions.
yeah
- Do it, do it, do it. You decided to do it. That's good.
- I kind of realized it.
- It left a meaning.
- It's left over. Left over?
- We have three minutes left of rehearsal.
- We've got three minutes left of rehearsal, so let's just do it on stage and don't get sundazed.
- Don't be relaxed.
- It's better if you don't get distracted and let your voice come out. Don't be lazy.
- Soon.
There must be a future in the blue sky.
I can't even hear the end.
When will it be over?
Nothing.
Nothing I've ever seen.Nothing I've ever seen before.
I couldn't remember.
in the human papers
in the middle of the paper
I've been looking for you.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'm looking forward to working with you all.
Thank you very much.
Second group is finished.
Okay.
Hi, I'm Sacchan!
Hello, Sachan!
Sacchan, you're doing well.
Sacchan, you worked hard.
Sacchan almost cried during rehearsal today.
Oh, no!
Oh, no! I cried!
I cried.
Why did you lie?
I was about to cry, but I held it in
It was no good
Aaah!
I'm surrounded by cute junior staff
I'm happy.
I'll do my best
I'll do my best.
Today's the last day.
You can just see it from here.
I'm so happy.
I'm glad.
I'm glad to have a junior who can say that.
I'll keep saying it.
Thank you.
Of course.
Go get ready.Go get ready.
Kyuuuu!
Squeak.
Wow.
Thank you!
Dodgy Marol, haha.
Are you okay?
Makeup?
Oh, you're in.
Ta-da!
Takosen.
I got a Kansai specialty.
Ta-da!
I got takoyaki, kushikatsu and
Shumai from Hourai!
I love this shrimp shaomai.
What are you eating, Mayu-tan?
I'm eating sweets.
Eat your dinner.
I just ate dinner.
After dinner.
Takoyaki... octopus balls.
After dinner...
I changed the sauce and mayo.
It's delicious.
Just now...
I just saw a lot of footage.
They're all so cute.
I'm going to eat.
Bon appétit!
Ta-da!
Yakubo and Mew!
Takosen!
I see you again.I can see you again.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Cute spider.
Look at this one, too.
It's the color of Nogizaka.
It's cute.
It's so cute!
I'm gonna eat it.
The colors are so similar.
Yui's hair color is good too
Clubman-chan!
Wow!
It's good.
It's fine.
I thought you were wearing makeup.
It's too well-done.
I thought it looked really good. I didn't.
I didn't.
This is Mieu Matsuo.
Mieux Matsuo.
You enjoyed it, didn't you?
Eat.
Thank you.
We ate.
This is the second day in Osaka. I thought it was yesterday's stage, but the fans in Osaka are so powerful that I hope I can raise the tension of the opening performance by several levels so that I won't be defeated.
And since today is the last day for Seira, I would like all the fans behind the live to cherish every moment of today and enjoy the show.
I hope you will enjoy every moment of the day.
I would like to end the show with everyone having a good time, so I would be happy if we could all enjoy the show with all our might. Thank you very much for your cooperation.
The act of shaking hands and putting together a handshake
I want to do my best to make today the brightest day of that day
I want to renew it with my thoughts.
Erica Hiaxa
Hiaxa Erica
Hiaxa, Erica.
You're going to kill me.
Hey, who's trying to kill me?Hey, who did this to you?
I don't know who he is.
I don't know who you are, but you need to find out.
Thank you for your time.
Oh, I wish I could go.
I wish I could go
You worked so hard
You looked great
You were so big when you were talking a minute ago.
Are you okay?
You say the nicest things.
Congratulations!
Congratulations.
I'm really grateful to all the seniors.
They are always so kind to me.
Thank you for being so nice to me.
Thank you for being so kind to me.
The juniors are kind to me, too.
And my classmates are so kind to me.
I love you so much. Thank you very much.
Three, two, one.
Yes, you can.
Yes, it was good. 3-2-1.
Three, two, one.
So, thank you for your hard work, Mr. Hayakawa.
complaints
none
Can I ask you to open your mouth?
The graduation ceremony is over!
I received flowers.
I was surrounded by so many kind members.Surrounded by amazingly kind members of the
The staff was also very kind to me.
It was a really happy day.
Above all, the fans were so warm and friendly.
You gave us a surprise "thank you" gift.
It was the most wonderful celebration I've ever seen.
It was the most wonderful celebration I've ever seen!
Thank you so much!